This area here, between the eyebrows, is a zone that indicates when someone truly
眉间这个区域，它指示着当一个人真正地
is experiencing suffering,
承受痛苦时，
or going through suffering in their life, whether it be physical, emotional, or otherwise,
或在生活中经历痛苦，无论是身体上、情感上还是其他方面的痛苦，
you will observe this here, and in the eyes as well; you can perceive the eye almost making a movement, like this.
你会在这里看到，眼睛里也会有，你会看到眼睛几乎在这样移动。
There is a specific geometry within the iris that can manifest in this manner, which...
虹膜中存在一种几何结构，它可以这样显现出来，它...
It is also an initiation point that is also related
这也是一个起始点，它也与...相关
with the...
与...
The brain's primordium, at the outset, is flat.
脑的原始形态，最初是扁平的。
And through the process of telencephalization, it undergoes this transformation.
通过端脑化过程，它会形成这种形态。
This is where the crista galli is established.
这就是鸡冠形成的地方。
It is a point of concentration.
这是一个集中点。
We call it the eye of clairvoyance.
我们称之为“千里眼之眼”。
You have 'voyance'.
你拥有通灵能力。
In this instance, one utilizes the other's emotions.
在这里，我们利用他人的情感。
I will interact with your astral plane.
我将与你的星光体层面互动。
And then, you have clairvoyance.
然后，你拥有千里眼能力。
That is to say, you begin to perceive the world entirely.
也就是说，你开始完全地看待世界。
from the perspective of the other. This implies perceiving their operational mechanisms. This, in itself, constitutes a form of clairvoyance.
从他人的角度。这意味着你看到他是如何运作的。这本身就是一种千里眼。
This occurs here. And then, you have the third and unique form of 'voyance', which is polyvoyance.
这发生在这里。然后，你拥有第三种也是独一无二的通灵能力，那就是多重通灵。
You
你
begin to perceive God or this divinity in everything. You have
开始在万物中看到上帝或这种神性。你拥有
an electromagnetic spectrum.
一个电磁光谱。
This is what is perceived. You see, if I have developed, in fact, it
这就是我们所看到的。你看，如果我成长了，实际上，这
is already quite significant. It is our rainbow
已经很不错了。这是我们的彩虹
of light.
光的。
However, observe what this represents as reality, you see, surrounding us.
但看看这代表着怎样的现实，你看，在我们周围。
All that exists, all these frequencies; the more one enhances their capacities,
所有这些，所有这些频率，你越是提升你的能力，
one can sometimes perceive phenomena slightly beyond the ordinary.
有时你就能看到一些超乎寻常的事物。
The eye will receive luminous information; thus, it will receive a photon.
眼睛将接收光信息，因此它将接收一个光子。
The very first layer that will be traversed will be the conjunctiva.
将被穿过的第一层将是结膜。
The second layer to be traversed will be the cornea.
第二层将被穿过的是角膜。
The cornea, which is the anterior portion...
角膜是...
...of the sclera, transparent.
巩膜前部透明的部分。
Then, you will have the passage through the pupil.
然后，光线将穿过瞳孔。
So, the first chamber anteriorly is the anterior chamber,
因此，前面的第一个房室是前房，
which contains aqueous humor.
含有房水。
The anterior chamber, the iris, with the pupil here, which
前房，虹膜，以及这里的瞳孔，光线将
allows passage.
穿过。
And here, you have a so-called posterior chamber,
在这里，你们有一个所谓的后房，
which still contains the same fluid.
仍然含有相同的液体。
But anteriorly here, you have what are called the ciliary bodies,
但在这里的前方，你们有所谓的睫状体，
which also produce [fluid].
它们也会产生。
fluid, and slightly posterior here to what is called the limbus, you will find
液体，而在巩膜缘的稍后方，你们将有
the canal
管道，
of Schlemm, or scleral venous sinus, which reabsorbs [fluid]. So, there
施莱姆管或巩膜窦，它会重吸收，因此
is continuously a fluid that
持续有液体
circulates here, which sustains and nourishes. Then it will traverse and encounter what is
在这里循环，维持生命并滋养，然后它会穿过并遇到
called the crystalline lens, responsible for accommodation. And at the level of the crystalline lens, the vitreous humor
我们所
traverses to
称之为晶状体，它负责调节，而在晶状体处，玻璃体液
reach my
穿过，以便
retina, which is composed of different layers. So, not only do I perceive only a small light spectrum, but I am still capable of detecting the smallest possible quantity of light, called a photon. Furthermore, I have a constricted field of vision.
到达我的
I have a
视网膜，它由不同层构成。因此，我不仅只接收一小部分
possible vision, which is a centered vision, and I also have a very interesting vision, which is peripheral vision. I must learn to utilize these two types of vision. Thus, a frequency,
光谱，但我仍然能够接收最小量的
a wave.
光，我们称之为光子。此外，我的视野是缩小的。
and a spectrum that, at maximum, varies in a foveal field of
我有
5 degrees,
一种可能的视觉，即中心视力，我还有一种非常有趣的视觉，
c'est la vision périphérique. Je dois apprendre à utiliser ces deux visions. Donc une fréquence,
那就是周边视力。我必须学习使用这两种视力。因此，一个频率，
une onde.
一个波。
et  un  spectre  qui,  maximum,  varie  en  fétrade  de
以及一个光谱，其最大变化范围为
5  degrés,
5度，
in fact, even regarding 23 degrees, but I will explain that a bit later.
实际上，甚至相对于23度，但我稍后会解释。
It is a 23-degree angle, like the orientation of your heart,
这是23度，就像您心脏的朝向，
like the orientation of the Earth, like the orientation of your inner ears.
就像地球的朝向，就像您内耳的朝向。
There are specific angulations within the body.
身体中存在特定的角度。
This will reach the retina, initiating what is known as the phenomenon of transduction,
它会到达视网膜，产生我们所说的转导现象，
converting photons into electrical signals.
将光子转化为电信号。
into a nervous impulse that will be transmitted to
转化为神经冲动，将被传输到
the left and to the right,
左侧和右侧，
for each eye, at the level of what is referred to as the LGN,
每次针对一只眼睛，在我们所说的外侧膝状体（CGE）层面，
i.e., the lateral geniculate nucleus,
也就是外侧膝状体，
which will provide an interpretation, demonstrating how it integrates this information,
它将给出一种解释，关于它如何整合这些信息，
parvocellular, koniocellular, magnocellular,
小细胞层、大细胞层、锥细胞层，
which represent specific types of information.
这些将是特定的信息。
Subsequently, once this process is complete...
然后它会接着来，一旦它...
It will then utilize what are known as the optic radiations to project towards the
它将通过我们所说的视辐射，前往
visual cortex, specifically above and below the calcarine fissure.
视觉皮层，位于距状裂的上方和下方。
This is very interesting and crucial to be able to localize.
非常有趣，知道其位置非常重要。
This renowned journey, from the eye, encompassing all the interpretation we observe here,
这段著名的旅程，眼睛，我们在这里看到的所有解释，
and these radiations projecting towards these cortical areas and towards the various
以及这些辐射到这些皮层区域以及到不同的
levels of interpretation.
解释层面。
which we will now examine in a bit more detail.
我们现在将详细了解。